{
    "LevelPacks": 
    [
        {
            "Name": "Level Pack A",
            "Levels":
            [
                {
                    "Name": "A-1",
                    "Sprite": "rose",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Mawar?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Merah"
                },
                {
                    "Name": "A-2",
                    "Sprite": "sky",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Langit?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Biru"
                },
                {
                    "Name": "A-3",
                    "Sprite": "leaf",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Daun?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Hijau"
                },
                {
                    "Name": "A-4",
                    "Sprite": "sun",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Matahari?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Kuning"
                },
                {
                    "Name": "A-5",
                    "Sprite": "ocean",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Laut?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Biru"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Name": "Level Pack B",
            "Levels":
            [
                {
                    "Name": "B-1",
                    "Sprite": "sky",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Langit?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Biru"
                },
                {
                    "Name": "B-2",
                    "Sprite": "leaf",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Daun?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Hijau"
                },
                {
                    "Name": "B-3",
                    "Sprite": "sun",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Matahari?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Kuning"
                },
                {
                    "Name": "B-4",
                    "Sprite": "ocean",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Laut?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Biru"
                },
                {
                    "Name": "B-5",
                    "Sprite": "rose",
                    "Question": "Warna dari Mawar?",
                    "Answers":
                    [
                        "Merah",
                        "Biru",
                        "Hijau",
                        "Kuning"
                    ],
                    "CorrectAnswer": "Merah"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}